quiz = {

  1 : {
    "question" : "Which BL couple uses the symbols sun and sunflower?  (Please write their couple name as one word!!!)",
    "answer"   : "mewgulf"
  },

  2 : {
    "question" : "P'Fighter in Why R U is played by who?",
    "answer"   : "zee"
  },

  3 : {
    "question" : "The show that dealt with soulmates, tragic past lives, forbidden love and acceptance and a shitstorm of tearjerkers that you probably watched in utter pain is ...",
    "answer"   : "until we meet again"
  },

  4 : {
    "question" : "Trick question BounPrem, PremBoun, or both?",
    "answer"   : ""
  },

  5 : {
    "question" : "A Filipino BL based during Covid that deals with coming out, the fear and reality behind online dating and alot of video games and streaming!",
    "answer"   : "gameboys"
  },

  6 : {
    "question" : "King from My Engineer was afraid of ...",
    "answer"   : "dogs"
  },

  7 : {
    "question" : "Tine's favorite band in 2gether was ...",
    "answer"   : "scrubb"
  },

  8 : {
    "question" : "A Korean BL about an actor and a chef living together.",
    "answer"   : "to my star"
  },

  9 : {
    "question" : "OffGun's most recent drama about gangs and police.",
    "answer"   : "not me"
  },

  10 : {
    "question" : "Which one of these is another BL actor  that Singto has acted with: a. Gun b. Ja c. Earth d. Ohm",
    "answer"   : "d"
  }
}